export default [
{
        id: 0,
        question: 'What is 34 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['18','17','24','21'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 1,
        question: 'What is 32 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['16','22','16','19'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 2,
        question: 'What is 32 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['16','20','26','23'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 3,
        question: 'What is 16 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['16','19','13','8'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 4,
        question: 'What is 14 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['17','7','23','20'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 5,
        question: 'What is 18 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['18','9','21','24'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 6,
        question: 'What is 32 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['16','13','10','7'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 7,
        question: 'What is 10 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['21','24','5','18'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 8,
        question: 'What is 30 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['10','7','13','15'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 9,
        question: 'What is 14 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['23','26','7','20'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 10,
        question: 'What is 38 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['19','16','19','13'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 11,
        question: 'What is 10 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['5','19','25','22'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 12,
        question: 'What is 16 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['22','16','8','19'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 13,
        question: 'What is 30 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['9','15','12','15'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 14,
        question: 'What is 28 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['14','19','16','13'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 15,
        question: 'What is 20 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['20','23','26','10'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 16,
        question: 'What is 12 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['6','12','6','9'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 17,
        question: 'What is 18 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['9','6','9','12'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 18,
        question: 'What is 32 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['10','13','16','16'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 19,
        question: 'What is 16 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['13','8','19','16'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 20,
        question: 'What is 16 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['11','8','14','17'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 21,
        question: 'What is 18 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['9','20','17','23'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 22,
        question: 'What is 20 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['16','19','10','22'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 23,
        question: 'What is 30 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['15','7','13','10'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 24,
        question: 'What is 32 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['16','25','22','19'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 25,
        question: 'What is 14 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['13','7','7','10'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 26,
        question: 'What is 30 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['19','25','15','22'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 27,
        question: 'What is 30 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['22','25','19','15'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 28,
        question: 'What is 22 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['15','18','11','12'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 29,
        question: 'What is 24 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['16','12','10','13'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 30,
        question: 'What is 16 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['18','15','12','8'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 31,
        question: 'What is 26 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['19','16','13','13'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 32,
        question: 'What is 10 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['12','15','5','18'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 33,
        question: 'What is 28 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['11','14','14','17'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 34,
        question: 'What is 34 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['7','13','10','17'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 35,
        question: 'What is 26 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['13','8','11','14'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 36,
        question: 'What is 28 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['8','14','11','14'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 37,
        question: 'What is 26 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['7','13','13','10'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 38,
        question: 'What is 38 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['19','16','13','19'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 39,
        question: 'What is 14 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['7','16','13','19'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 40,
        question: 'What is 16 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['15','12','18','8'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 41,
        question: 'What is 22 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['13','19','11','16'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 42,
        question: 'What is 38 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['8','11','19','14'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 43,
        question: 'What is 14 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['9','6','7','12'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 44,
        question: 'What is 26 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['13','12','15','9'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 45,
        question: 'What is 20 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['10','20','23','17'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 46,
        question: 'What is 20 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['10','10','16','13'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 47,
        question: 'What is 10 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['15','5','18','12'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 48,
        question: 'What is 34 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['9','12','17','15'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 49,
        question: 'What is 34 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['13','10','17','16'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 50,
        question: 'What is 26 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['17','11','14','13'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 51,
        question: 'What is 18 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['11','14','9','17'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 52,
        question: 'What is 30 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['21','24','15','18'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 53,
        question: 'What is 34 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['18','24','17','21'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 54,
        question: 'What is 38 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['18','19','21','24'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 55,
        question: 'What is 34 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['19','17','22','25'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 56,
        question: 'What is 10 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['25','19','5','22'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 57,
        question: 'What is 28 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['17','11','14','14'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 58,
        question: 'What is 14 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['23','20','26','7'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 59,
        question: 'What is 24 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['8','14','12','11'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 60,
        question: 'What is 38 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['24','21','18','19'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 61,
        question: 'What is 32 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['14','11','17','16'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 62,
        question: 'What is 14 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['22','19','25','7'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 63,
        question: 'What is 26 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['20','13','23','17'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 64,
        question: 'What is 26 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['10','13','16','13'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 65,
        question: 'What is 16 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['6','12','9','8'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 66,
        question: 'What is 20 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['18','21','10','24'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 67,
        question: 'What is 14 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['18','15','12','7'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 68,
        question: 'What is 14 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['7','21','18','15'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 69,
        question: 'What is 24 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['15','12','18','12'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 70,
        question: 'What is 26 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['25','19','13','22'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 71,
        question: 'What is 24 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['15','12','12','9'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 72,
        question: 'What is 16 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['20','17','14','8'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 73,
        question: 'What is 34 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['19','17','16','22'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 74,
        question: 'What is 24 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['17','11','14','12'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 75,
        question: 'What is 30 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['15','16','19','22'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 76,
        question: 'What is 36 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['16','22','18','19'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 77,
        question: 'What is 14 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['23','17','20','7'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 78,
        question: 'What is 36 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['18','15','12','18'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 79,
        question: 'What is 10 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['11','8','14','5'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 80,
        question: 'What is 16 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['19','22','16','8'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 81,
        question: 'What is 28 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['17','14','14','11'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 82,
        question: 'What is 34 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['18','17','12','15'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 83,
        question: 'What is 28 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['19','14','22','16'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 84,
        question: 'What is 10 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['5','18','21','24'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 85,
        question: 'What is 26 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['16','13','19','13'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 86,
        question: 'What is 30 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['23','20','15','26'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 87,
        question: 'What is 16 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['16','10','13','8'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 88,
        question: 'What is 10 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['19','16','5','13'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 89,
        question: 'What is 34 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['17','18','21','15'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 90,
        question: 'What is 38 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['12','18','19','15'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 91,
        question: 'What is 14 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['7','13','10','7'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 92,
        question: 'What is 20 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['22','10','25','19'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 93,
        question: 'What is 32 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['22','19','25','16'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 94,
        question: 'What is 20 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['23','10','26','20'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 95,
        question: 'What is 34 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['15','18','21','17'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 96,
        question: 'What is 36 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['15','18','18','21'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 97,
        question: 'What is 28 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['12','9','14','15'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 98,
        question: 'What is 30 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['26','23','15','20'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 99,
        question: 'What is 20 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['10','19','16','22'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 100,
        question: 'What is 38 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['23','19','17','20'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 101,
        question: 'What is 22 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['26','11','23','20'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 102,
        question: 'What is 30 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['12','9','15','15'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 103,
        question: 'What is 34 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['17','20','17','23'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 104,
        question: 'What is 16 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['17','14','11','8'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 105,
        question: 'What is 24 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['17','11','14','12'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 106,
        question: 'What is 38 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['19','10','13','7'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 107,
        question: 'What is 12 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['6','9','15','12'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 108,
        question: 'What is 16 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['18','12','8','15'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 109,
        question: 'What is 34 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['26','23','20','17'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 110,
        question: 'What is 30 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['13','15','10','16'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 111,
        question: 'What is 22 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['11','10','13','7'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 112,
        question: 'What is 26 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['13','19','16','13'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 113,
        question: 'What is 26 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['15','13','9','12'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 114,
        question: 'What is 26 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['15','18','21','13'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 115,
        question: 'What is 34 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['23','20','26','17'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 116,
        question: 'What is 30 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['19','16','15','13'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 117,
        question: 'What is 28 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['14','25','22','19'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 118,
        question: 'What is 14 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['7','14','17','20'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 119,
        question: 'What is 36 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['9','18','12','6'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 120,
        question: 'What is 28 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['14','19','22','25'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 121,
        question: 'What is 34 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['20','17','14','17'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 122,
        question: 'What is 14 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['18','15','21','7'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 123,
        question: 'What is 36 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['20','23','26','18'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 124,
        question: 'What is 14 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['7','23','20','17'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 125,
        question: 'What is 14 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['13','16','10','7'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 126,
        question: 'What is 24 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['23','17','12','20'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 127,
        question: 'What is 36 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['18','18','15','21'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 128,
        question: 'What is 32 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['14','17','20','16'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 129,
        question: 'What is 38 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['9','19','12','15'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 130,
        question: 'What is 12 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['6','12','6','9'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 131,
        question: 'What is 36 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['18','14','11','17'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 132,
        question: 'What is 26 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['13','23','20','26'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 133,
        question: 'What is 20 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['10','10','13','7'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 134,
        question: 'What is 16 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['12','8','9','6'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 135,
        question: 'What is 26 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['13','22','19','25'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 136,
        question: 'What is 28 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['14','21','18','24'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 137,
        question: 'What is 20 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['17','14','10','11'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 138,
        question: 'What is 28 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['19','14','16','22'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 139,
        question: 'What is 12 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['7','6','10','13'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 140,
        question: 'What is 10 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['5','20','14','17'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 141,
        question: 'What is 26 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['13','12','15','9'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 142,
        question: 'What is 20 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['20','23','17','10'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 143,
        question: 'What is 22 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['11','8','11','14'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 144,
        question: 'What is 30 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['15','14','8','11'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 145,
        question: 'What is 18 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['7','13','10','9'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 146,
        question: 'What is 24 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['12','12','9','15'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 147,
        question: 'What is 38 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['19','25','19','22'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 148,
        question: 'What is 28 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['16','19','14','13'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 149,
        question: 'What is 30 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['14','15','17','11'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 150,
        question: 'What is 12 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['6','22','16','19'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 151,
        question: 'What is 34 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['9','15','12','17'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 152,
        question: 'What is 12 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['17','14','6','20'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 153,
        question: 'What is 12 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['16','19','6','22'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 154,
        question: 'What is 38 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['19','21','24','18'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 155,
        question: 'What is 28 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['22','25','19','14'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 156,
        question: 'What is 30 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['15','14','11','17'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 157,
        question: 'What is 24 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['10','7','13','12'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 158,
        question: 'What is 32 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['16','14','17','20'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 159,
        question: 'What is 14 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['7','19','16','13'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 160,
        question: 'What is 14 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['15','7','9','12'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 161,
        question: 'What is 26 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['13','24','18','21'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 162,
        question: 'What is 30 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['12','18','15','15'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 163,
        question: 'What is 10 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['9','15','12','5'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 164,
        question: 'What is 36 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['12','18','15','9'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 165,
        question: 'What is 30 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['17','15','11','14'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 166,
        question: 'What is 38 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['19','15','18','12'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 167,
        question: 'What is 30 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['19','22','15','16'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 168,
        question: 'What is 16 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['21','18','15','8'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 169,
        question: 'What is 30 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['20','14','17','15'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 170,
        question: 'What is 24 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['17','20','14','12'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 171,
        question: 'What is 34 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['17','17','14','20'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 172,
        question: 'What is 26 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['7','13','13','10'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 173,
        question: 'What is 20 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['10','12','15','18'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 174,
        question: 'What is 28 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['10','16','13','14'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 175,
        question: 'What is 20 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['10','17','20','23'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 176,
        question: 'What is 16 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['18','15','12','8'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 177,
        question: 'What is 14 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['7','13','10','7'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 178,
        question: 'What is 18 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['9','26','20','23'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 179,
        question: 'What is 22 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['21','18','11','15'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 180,
        question: 'What is 30 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['15','18','15','12'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 181,
        question: 'What is 24 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['15','12','21','18'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 182,
        question: 'What is 26 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['15','21','18','13'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 183,
        question: 'What is 36 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['19','16','18','13'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 184,
        question: 'What is 22 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['16','11','19','22'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 185,
        question: 'What is 32 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['18','16','12','15'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 186,
        question: 'What is 28 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['14','14','17','20'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 187,
        question: 'What is 10 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['11','14','17','5'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 188,
        question: 'What is 32 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['18','16','15','12'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 189,
        question: 'What is 32 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['15','9','16','12'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 190,
        question: 'What is 12 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['9','6','15','12'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 191,
        question: 'What is 30 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['19','22','16','15'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 192,
        question: 'What is 38 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['19','6','9','12'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 193,
        question: 'What is 22 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['8','11','14','11'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 194,
        question: 'What is 38 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['21','19','18','15'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 195,
        question: 'What is 26 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['16','19','13','13'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 196,
        question: 'What is 10 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['14','11','17','5'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 197,
        question: 'What is 10 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['12','9','5','6'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 198,
        question: 'What is 22 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['20','23','17','11'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 199,
        question: 'What is 38 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['22','19','25','19'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 200,
        question: 'What is 16 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['11','17','14','8'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 201,
        question: 'What is 22 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['16','11','22','19'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 202,
        question: 'What is 22 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['11','18','15','21'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 203,
        question: 'What is 26 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['13','20','26','23'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 204,
        question: 'What is 38 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['16','19','13','10'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 205,
        question: 'What is 16 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['16','10','13','8'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 206,
        question: 'What is 12 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['18','6','15','21'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 207,
        question: 'What is 26 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['23','13','17','20'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 208,
        question: 'What is 18 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['20','9','23','26'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 209,
        question: 'What is 10 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['9','15','5','12'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 210,
        question: 'What is 38 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['17','19','14','20'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 211,
        question: 'What is 16 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['6','12','8','9'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 212,
        question: 'What is 26 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['6','13','12','9'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 213,
        question: 'What is 34 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['26','20','17','23'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 214,
        question: 'What is 30 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['18','12','15','15'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 215,
        question: 'What is 20 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['20','10','23','26'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 216,
        question: 'What is 16 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['8','18','12','15'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 217,
        question: 'What is 28 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['22','19','25','14'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 218,
        question: 'What is 38 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['10','13','7','19'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 219,
        question: 'What is 38 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['14','19','20','17'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 220,
        question: 'What is 10 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['12','5','18','15'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 221,
        question: 'What is 38 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['19','16','19','13'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 222,
        question: 'What is 16 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['8','20','17','14'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 223,
        question: 'What is 12 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['6','20','23','26'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 224,
        question: 'What is 12 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['6','21','18','24'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 225,
        question: 'What is 20 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['14','17','20','10'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 226,
        question: 'What is 16 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['10','16','8','13'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 227,
        question: 'What is 10 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['5','20','26','23'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 228,
        question: 'What is 16 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['8','10','7','13'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 229,
        question: 'What is 22 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['12','18','15','11'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 230,
        question: 'What is 16 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['8','23','20','17'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 231,
        question: 'What is 18 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['14','8','11','9'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 232,
        question: 'What is 28 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['13','16','14','19'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 233,
        question: 'What is 38 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['15','12','18','19'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 234,
        question: 'What is 28 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['11','14','17','14'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 235,
        question: 'What is 16 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['8','23','20','26'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 236,
        question: 'What is 10 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['5','10','7','13'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 237,
        question: 'What is 26 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['14','11','8','13'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 238,
        question: 'What is 16 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['8','20','14','17'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 239,
        question: 'What is 10 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['5','17','11','14'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 240,
        question: 'What is 22 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['7','11','10','13'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 241,
        question: 'What is 36 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['7','10','13','18'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 242,
        question: 'What is 26 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['16','13','19','13'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 243,
        question: 'What is 24 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['16','13','19','12'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 244,
        question: 'What is 24 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['14','11','12','17'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 245,
        question: 'What is 38 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['19','18','24','21'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 246,
        question: 'What is 30 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['13','7','10','15'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 247,
        question: 'What is 22 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['22','16','11','19'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 248,
        question: 'What is 22 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['11','23','20','26'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 249,
        question: 'What is 16 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['20','14','8','17'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 250,
        question: 'What is 12 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['24','21','18','6'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 251,
        question: 'What is 20 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['13','10','10','16'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 252,
        question: 'What is 34 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['21','17','18','15'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 253,
        question: 'What is 24 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['16','13','19','12'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 254,
        question: 'What is 24 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['17','20','14','12'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 255,
        question: 'What is 24 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['26','20','12','23'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 256,
        question: 'What is 22 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['11','13','19','16'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 257,
        question: 'What is 38 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['10','19','13','16'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 258,
        question: 'What is 24 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['16','13','10','12'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 259,
        question: 'What is 14 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['7','26','23','20'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 260,
        question: 'What is 12 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['12','9','6','6'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 261,
        question: 'What is 30 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['12','15','15','18'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 262,
        question: 'What is 10 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['11','17','5','14'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 263,
        question: 'What is 14 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['7','21','24','18'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 264,
        question: 'What is 16 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['14','17','20','8'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 265,
        question: 'What is 10 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['18','15','5','12'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 266,
        question: 'What is 22 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['17','11','23','20'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 267,
        question: 'What is 18 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['16','9','19','22'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 268,
        question: 'What is 20 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['15','9','12','10'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 269,
        question: 'What is 20 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['19','13','10','16'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 270,
        question: 'What is 36 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['11','18','14','8'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 271,
        question: 'What is 30 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['20','15','26','23'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 272,
        question: 'What is 12 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['15','12','6','18'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 273,
        question: 'What is 20 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['7','10','10','13'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 274,
        question: 'What is 12 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['12','6','6','9'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 275,
        question: 'What is 12 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['22','19','6','16'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 276,
        question: 'What is 36 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['14','18','17','11'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 277,
        question: 'What is 24 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['23','12','20','17'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 278,
        question: 'What is 32 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['13','16','19','16'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 279,
        question: 'What is 32 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['16','19','16','13'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 280,
        question: 'What is 26 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['15','12','13','9'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 281,
        question: 'What is 20 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['10','14','17','11'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 282,
        question: 'What is 28 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['14','23','17','20'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 283,
        question: 'What is 38 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['19','10','13','16'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 284,
        question: 'What is 36 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['22','18','25','19'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 285,
        question: 'What is 34 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['26','23','20','17'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 286,
        question: 'What is 10 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['17','14','5','11'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 287,
        question: 'What is 12 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['13','16','19','6'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 288,
        question: 'What is 10 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['6','9','5','12'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 289,
        question: 'What is 26 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['24','18','21','13'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 290,
        question: 'What is 36 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['22','19','25','18'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 291,
        question: 'What is 32 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['16','18','24','21'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 292,
        question: 'What is 30 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['7','13','15','10'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 293,
        question: 'What is 34 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['14','20','17','17'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 294,
        question: 'What is 18 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['9','22','25','19'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 295,
        question: 'What is 30 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['10','16','15','13'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 296,
        question: 'What is 18 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['9','20','17','23'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 297,
        question: 'What is 28 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['14','19','16','13'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 298,
        question: 'What is 18 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['25','22','19','9'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 299,
        question: 'What is 14 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['22','7','16','19'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 300,
        question: 'What is 12 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['20','17','14','6'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 301,
        question: 'What is 16 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['11','8','8','14'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 302,
        question: 'What is 18 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['9','10','13','7'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 303,
        question: 'What is 18 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['9','14','17','11'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 304,
        question: 'What is 36 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['23','18','26','20'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 305,
        question: 'What is 20 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['17','23','10','20'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 306,
        question: 'What is 10 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['24','21','5','18'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 307,
        question: 'What is 34 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['22','19','25','17'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 308,
        question: 'What is 38 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['20','26','23','19'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 309,
        question: 'What is 32 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['10','16','13','16'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 310,
        question: 'What is 34 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['17','23','17','20'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 311,
        question: 'What is 34 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['15','9','12','17'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 312,
        question: 'What is 34 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['17','11','17','14'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 313,
        question: 'What is 20 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['10','9','12','6'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 314,
        question: 'What is 20 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['11','14','10','17'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 315,
        question: 'What is 26 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['18','21','13','15'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 316,
        question: 'What is 16 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['8','16','19','22'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 317,
        question: 'What is 36 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['21','18','15','18'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 318,
        question: 'What is 32 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['24','18','21','16'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 319,
        question: 'What is 28 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['14','14','11','8'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 320,
        question: 'What is 34 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['17','7','10','13'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 321,
        question: 'What is 28 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['9','6','14','12'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 322,
        question: 'What is 14 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['7','11','14','17'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 323,
        question: 'What is 22 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['19','11','13','16'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 324,
        question: 'What is 16 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['8','19','25','22'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 325,
        question: 'What is 18 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['22','9','19','16'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 326,
        question: 'What is 34 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['13','17','10','7'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 327,
        question: 'What is 14 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['21','18','24','7'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 328,
        question: 'What is 16 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['15','9','8','12'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 329,
        question: 'What is 36 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['13','16','18','10'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 330,
        question: 'What is 30 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['15','13','10','7'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 331,
        question: 'What is 14 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['12','15','9','7'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 332,
        question: 'What is 24 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['20','12','17','14'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 333,
        question: 'What is 12 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['17','6','14','11'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 334,
        question: 'What is 36 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['18','24','21','18'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 335,
        question: 'What is 20 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['10','23','26','20'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 336,
        question: 'What is 30 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['14','11','15','17'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 337,
        question: 'What is 26 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['14','8','13','11'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 338,
        question: 'What is 28 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['14','6','12','9'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 339,
        question: 'What is 24 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['12','17','14','11'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 340,
        question: 'What is 22 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['23','11','20','17'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 341,
        question: 'What is 16 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['18','21','24','8'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 342,
        question: 'What is 12 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['20','23','6','17'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 343,
        question: 'What is 38 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['17','11','14','19'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 344,
        question: 'What is 30 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['20','14','15','17'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 345,
        question: 'What is 38 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['9','12','19','6'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 346,
        question: 'What is 20 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['15','10','12','9'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 347,
        question: 'What is 28 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['15','21','14','18'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 348,
        question: 'What is 36 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['18','11','17','14'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 349,
        question: 'What is 32 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['14','17','16','20'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 350,
        question: 'What is 16 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['17','8','14','11'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 351,
        question: 'What is 28 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['14','21','24','18'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 352,
        question: 'What is 28 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['21','24','14','18'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 353,
        question: 'What is 22 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['15','11','9','12'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 354,
        question: 'What is 12 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['6','11','8','14'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 355,
        question: 'What is 14 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['16','7','22','19'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 356,
        question: 'What is 38 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['14','17','19','11'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 357,
        question: 'What is 20 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['18','24','21','10'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 358,
        question: 'What is 14 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['24','18','7','21'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 359,
        question: 'What is 28 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['13','14','16','10'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 360,
        question: 'What is 28 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['14','17','14','11'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 361,
        question: 'What is 32 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['16','24','21','18'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 362,
        question: 'What is 36 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['22','18','19','16'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 363,
        question: 'What is 32 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['14','17','11','16'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 364,
        question: 'What is 38 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['19','26','23','20'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 365,
        question: 'What is 38 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['17','11','14','19'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 366,
        question: 'What is 28 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['14','22','19','16'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 367,
        question: 'What is 36 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['20','23','18','17'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 368,
        question: 'What is 32 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['24','21','16','18'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 369,
        question: 'What is 28 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['22','14','19','16'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 370,
        question: 'What is 26 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['7','10','13','13'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 371,
        question: 'What is 14 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['9','6','7','12'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 372,
        question: 'What is 22 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['11','23','20','17'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 373,
        question: 'What is 34 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['12','9','6','17'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 374,
        question: 'What is 16 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['13','16','10','8'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 375,
        question: 'What is 16 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['8','16','22','19'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 376,
        question: 'What is 30 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['13','10','15','7'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 377,
        question: 'What is 10 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['16','22','5','19'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 378,
        question: 'What is 16 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['8','14','11','8'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 379,
        question: 'What is 30 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['16','22','19','15'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 380,
        question: 'What is 32 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['11','14','16','8'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 381,
        question: 'What is 14 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['16','13','10','7'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 382,
        question: 'What is 10 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['15','18','5','12'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 383,
        question: 'What is 12 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['14','8','11','6'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 384,
        question: 'What is 32 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['22','25','19','16'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 385,
        question: 'What is 16 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['14','8','11','8'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 386,
        question: 'What is 32 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['8','14','11','16'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 387,
        question: 'What is 18 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['18','24','9','21'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 388,
        question: 'What is 30 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['25','19','15','22'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 389,
        question: 'What is 22 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['12','9','11','6'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 390,
        question: 'What is 22 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['9','6','12','11'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 391,
        question: 'What is 34 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['19','13','17','16'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 392,
        question: 'What is 14 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['17','7','20','23'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 393,
        question: 'What is 38 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['19','17','20','23'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 394,
        question: 'What is 18 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['9','17','14','20'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 395,
        question: 'What is 12 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['6','9','15','12'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 396,
        question: 'What is 14 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['25','19','7','22'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 397,
        question: 'What is 34 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['20','14','17','17'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 398,
        question: 'What is 24 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['22','25','19','12'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 399,
        question: 'What is 32 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['10','16','16','13'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 400,
        question: 'What is 22 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['17','14','11','20'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 401,
        question: 'What is 38 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['22','16','19','19'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 402,
        question: 'What is 32 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['21','16','18','15'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 403,
        question: 'What is 36 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['16','18','19','13'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 404,
        question: 'What is 10 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['23','26','5','20'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 405,
        question: 'What is 38 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['14','11','8','19'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 406,
        question: 'What is 20 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['10','24','18','21'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 407,
        question: 'What is 24 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['12','8','11','14'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 408,
        question: 'What is 18 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['10','9','16','13'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 409,
        question: 'What is 14 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['18','21','15','7'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 410,
        question: 'What is 30 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['20','26','15','23'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 411,
        question: 'What is 32 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['20','23','26','16'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 412,
        question: 'What is 16 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['16','8','19','13'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 413,
        question: 'What is 34 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['21','18','17','15'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 414,
        question: 'What is 16 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['12','8','6','9'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 415,
        question: 'What is 38 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['19','15','18','21'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 416,
        question: 'What is 30 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['15','15','12','9'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 417,
        question: 'What is 16 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['16','22','19','8'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 418,
        question: 'What is 26 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['16','13','19','13'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 419,
        question: 'What is 24 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['11','17','14','12'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 420,
        question: 'What is 38 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['25','19','22','19'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 421,
        question: 'What is 18 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['9','19','22','16'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 422,
        question: 'What is 22 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['11','20','14','17'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 423,
        question: 'What is 20 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['12','18','10','15'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 424,
        question: 'What is 28 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['14','16','19','13'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 425,
        question: 'What is 36 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['9','12','18','6'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 426,
        question: 'What is 34 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['12','17','9','15'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 427,
        question: 'What is 20 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['14','10','20','17'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 428,
        question: 'What is 10 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['12','15','18','5'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 429,
        question: 'What is 14 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['21','18','24','7'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 430,
        question: 'What is 20 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['10','21','24','18'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 431,
        question: 'What is 16 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['23','8','17','20'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 432,
        question: 'What is 28 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['12','14','18','15'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 433,
        question: 'What is 38 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['14','17','11','19'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 434,
        question: 'What is 22 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['7','13','10','11'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 435,
        question: 'What is 20 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['10','15','12','18'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 436,
        question: 'What is 24 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['15','12','9','12'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 437,
        question: 'What is 18 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['12','9','15','18'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 438,
        question: 'What is 36 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['7','10','18','13'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 439,
        question: 'What is 18 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['10','16','13','9'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 440,
        question: 'What is 34 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['9','17','15','12'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 441,
        question: 'What is 20 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['10','24','21','18'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 442,
        question: 'What is 22 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['22','19','25','11'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 443,
        question: 'What is 28 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['14','11','8','14'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 444,
        question: 'What is 12 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['6','19','16','13'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 445,
        question: 'What is 18 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['13','19','16','9'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 446,
        question: 'What is 36 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['8','18','11','14'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 447,
        question: 'What is 12 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['19','6','16','13'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 448,
        question: 'What is 20 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['14','17','20','10'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 449,
        question: 'What is 30 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['15','6','12','9'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 450,
        question: 'What is 30 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['21','18','15','15'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 451,
        question: 'What is 30 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['26','15','23','20'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 452,
        question: 'What is 20 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['24','18','21','10'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 453,
        question: 'What is 36 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['18','24','18','21'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 454,
        question: 'What is 26 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['13','16','19','13'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 455,
        question: 'What is 24 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['20','17','23','12'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 456,
        question: 'What is 36 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['18','11','17','14'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 457,
        question: 'What is 20 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['10','12','6','9'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 458,
        question: 'What is 34 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['17','14','11','17'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 459,
        question: 'What is 30 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['19','22','15','25'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 460,
        question: 'What is 32 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['13','7','16','10'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 461,
        question: 'What is 10 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['18','15','21','5'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 462,
        question: 'What is 34 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['24','17','18','21'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 463,
        question: 'What is 16 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['17','8','14','20'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 464,
        question: 'What is 24 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['23','12','17','20'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 465,
        question: 'What is 24 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['14','11','17','12'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 466,
        question: 'What is 22 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['14','17','11','20'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 467,
        question: 'What is 10 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['5','26','23','20'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 468,
        question: 'What is 16 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['21','18','8','24'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 469,
        question: 'What is 24 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['12','7','10','13'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 470,
        question: 'What is 22 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['11','14','11','17'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 471,
        question: 'What is 12 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['18','15','21','6'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 472,
        question: 'What is 14 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['13','7','10','7'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 473,
        question: 'What is 14 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['7','18','21','15'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 474,
        question: 'What is 10 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['15','5','9','12'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 475,
        question: 'What is 36 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['13','19','18','16'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 476,
        question: 'What is 18 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['20','17','14','9'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 477,
        question: 'What is 36 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['13','16','18','10'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 478,
        question: 'What is 12 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['18','6','12','15'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 479,
        question: 'What is 10 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['5','23','17','20'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 480,
        question: 'What is 32 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['13','16','10','16'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 481,
        question: 'What is 26 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['15','13','12','18'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 482,
        question: 'What is 30 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['12','9','15','15'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 483,
        question: 'What is 14 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['7','6','12','9'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 484,
        question: 'What is 36 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['13','16','10','18'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 485,
        question: 'What is 20 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['15','18','21','10'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 486,
        question: 'What is 10 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['5','18','21','24'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 487,
        question: 'What is 24 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['17','14','12','20'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 488,
        question: 'What is 14 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['16','7','19','13'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 489,
        question: 'What is 18 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['12','15','18','9'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 490,
        question: 'What is 28 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['14','13','10','7'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 491,
        question: 'What is 24 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['16','12','22','19'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 492,
        question: 'What is 20 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['19','16','13','10'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 493,
        question: 'What is 22 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['13','11','16','10'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 494,
        question: 'What is 38 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['19','13','19','16'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 495,
        question: 'What is 34 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['12','17','6','9'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 496,
        question: 'What is 38 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['17','14','19','20'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 497,
        question: 'What is 16 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['7','8','13','10'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 498,
        question: 'What is 36 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['18','21','18','24'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 499,
        question: 'What is 14 / 2 ?',
        answers: ['15','7','12','9'],
        correct: 2

    },
]
